<resources>
    <string name="app_name">City Tour Tabbed Android App</string>
    <string name="Momuments">Monuments</string>
    <string name="Restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="IT_Companies">IT Companies</string>
    <string name="Libararies">Libararies</string>
    <string name="place_image_discription">An Image for the place you are currentyl viewing</string>
    <string name="MadaSaleh">Mada\'in Saleh</string>
    <string name="MadaSalehDescripttion">Mada\'in Saleh, also called \"Al-Hijr\" or \"Hegra\", is an archaeological site located in the Sector of Al-`Ula within Al Madinah Region, the Hejaz, Saudi Arabia. A majority of the remains date from the Nabatean kingdom.</string>
    <string name="MadaSalehAddress">Al-Hijr Hegra</string>
    <string name="Khaybar">Khaybar</string>
    <string name="KhaybarLocation">Khaybar City</string>
    <string name="KhaybarDescription">Khaybar is the name of an oasis some 153 km to the north of Medina, Saudi Arabia. Before the rise of Islam, this fortress town had been inhabited by Jewish tribes; it fell to Muslim forces in 629 AD.</string>
    <string name="MasmakFort">Masmak Fort</string>
    <string name="MasmakLocation">Riyadh, KSA</string>
    <string name="MasmakDescription">Masmak Fort Masmak castle.jpg General information Town or city\tRiyadh Country\tSaudi Arabia Construction started\t1865 The Masmak (Arabic: قصر المصمك‎, translit. Qaṣr al-Maṣmak) is a clay and mud-brick fort, with four watchtowers and thick walls, founded on stone blocks, lying in the center of Riyadh, in the old quarters. This building played a major part in the kingdom\'s history, as it was here that the recapture of Riyadh, led by Ibn Saud, occurred on 14 January 1902.</string>
    <string name="KFLIb">King Fahd Public Library.</string>
    <string name="KFLibDesc">On King Abdullah Road, just before Salam Mall, is the newly opened King Fahd Public Library. It has the biggest collection of books in Jeddah. They have a section for women and children with regular activities for them. It is very spacious and they have a play are for kids. They are open till 8pm in the evening.</string>
    <string name="MinstLib">Ministry of Education Library at al Ballad</string>
    <string name="MinstLibDescc">On Hail Street, at the corner of the Egypt Air building, is the Ministry of Education and inside, they have a library. I have only heard that it is public but never been there. I have been told they have only educational books.</string>
    <string name="KHLib">Khozam Park Public Library</string>
    <string name="KHLibDesc">This is the old public library in Old Jeddah. It is located at Khozam Park in al Nozhla al Yamaniyya area next to the Islamic Development bank near the water tower. It is behind the Jeddah TV station. Click the link above for the coordinates.</string>
    <string name="uxbert">UXBERT</string>
    <string name="uxbertdesc">KSA\'s leading UX consultancy creating stunning and positive user experiences. We cover usability testing, web, ecommerce, mobile and everything in between.</string>
    <string name="sit">XYZ Tech</string>
    <string name="sitedesc">Saudi Information Technology (SIT) is one of the specialized Saudi companies in the field of information technology that offers integrated solutions and technical</string>
    <string name="KFLibLoc">Olaya St, Al Olaya، Al Olaya, Riyadh 12211</string>
    <string name="MinstLibLoc">AL Balad Sub Municipal. location</string>
    <string name="KHLibLoc">8251 الظهيرة، Al Futah, Riyadh 12632</string>
    <string name="uxbertloc">Olaya St, Al Olaya, Nemer Center 1, Corner of Olaya , Musa Bin Nusair Street، Riyadh 12214</string>
    <string name="sitloc">طريق الملك فهد - العليا، Al Olaya, Riyadh 12214</string>
    <string name="alourjuan">‪Al Orjouan‬</string>
    <string name="alourjuanLoc">‪The Ritz-Carlton, Riyadh‬</string>
    <string name="alourjuanDesc">كانت تجربة مميزة ... يوم الاربعاء مخصص للأطعمة التركية ... المكان جميل جدا ... الطعام و المشروبات فخمة و لذيذة ... الموظفين ودودين و محترمين ... الشيفات محترفين ... أشكر الأخ ممدوح على حسن الضيافة و الاستقبال و الوداع ... أرغب بتجربته مرة أخرى و أدعوا الاخرين لتجربته</string>
    <string name="globe">‪The Globe‬</string>
    <string name="globeloc">Al Faisaliah Tower, King Fahad Road</string>
    <string name="globedesc">مطعم The Globe .. من أكثر المطاعم المميزة في العالم..و يسمى مطعم البلوره و هذا المطعم هو ما بداخل البلوره التي تعلو برج الفيصليه و هو ثلاث ادوار و بالحجز المسبق لانه زحمه ولازم تحجز</string>
</resources>
